Erich Maria Remarque Papers, 1918-2000 (bulk 1950s - 1980s) MSS.095
Fales Library and Special Collections
- 2003 Accretion
  - Series I: Literary properties, 244336
    - Subseries M: Spark of Life, 244795
      - Correspondence and memos, 1951-1952; 245356 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - British copyright - correspondence, 1951-1952; 245357 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Condensation rights to Omnibrook - correspondence, memos, notes, 1952; 245358 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Newspaper clip, 1952; 245360 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Dramatic production contract and collaboration contract with Jose Ferrer, 1952-1953; 245361 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Reviews, promotional materials, 1951-1952; 245362 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Accounts, 1952-1955; 245363 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Foreign inquiries - correspondence, memos, notes, 1952-1955; 245364 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Drafts, extra copies notes related to agreement with Appleton, 1951-1964; 245365 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Letter from Library of Congress about manuscript donation, 1965; 245366 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Letter of agreement, memorandum of agreement and copy of agreement with Appleton, 1951-1968; 245367 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence and memos about agreement with Appleton, 1951-1971; 245369 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, notes and drafts related to agreements with Appleton, New American Library, and Hutchinson & Co. Includes Memorandum of Agreement with Hutchinson & Co. for British publication rights, 1951-1971; 245373 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence and memos, 1980-1981; 245374 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Manuscript (1 of 4), undated; 245376 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Manuscript (2 of 4), undated; 245453 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Manuscript (3 of 4), undated; 245454 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Manuscript (4 of 4), undated; 245455 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Subseries N: Three Comrades, 244796
      - Little Brown correspondence with copy of 1931 contract and 1936 letter of agreement, undated, 1961-1986; 245473 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Contract with Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer (photostat of 1936 original), undated; 245456 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Contract with Loew's and copyright certificate (photostat of 1941-1942 originals), undated; 245457 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Contract with Popular Library, 1953; 245458 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence with Jean-Marie D'amat regarding dispute with Popular Library, 1957; 245459 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Agreement with Metro-Goldwyn-Meyer, 1965; 245460 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence and memos, 1948-1968; 245461 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Cheap reprint rights, 1952-1969; 245463 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Popular Library reprint rights - drafts, 1953-1969; 245464 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Royalty statements and correspondence, 1953-1974; 245465 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - German rights - correspondence, 1976; 245467 (Box 12, Folder 14)
        In German with partial translation.
      - Letter about Metro-Goldwyn Meyer screenplay rights, 1976; 245468 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Royalty Statements - Litton Educational Publishing Co., 1970-1979; 245469 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Publishing permissions, 1977-1981; 245470 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Royalty statements - Southern Illinois University Press, 1979-1981; 245472 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Royalty statements, 1984, 1986; 245474 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Southern Illinois Press - correspondence and royalty statements, 1983-1989; 245475 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Subseries O: A Time to Love and a Time to Die (aka A Time to Live and a Time to Die), 244797
      - Agreement with Harcourt, Brace and Company (photocopy of 1954 original), undated; 245477 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence and marketing materials, 1971; 245498 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Permissions, 1978-1980; 245790 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Copyright correspondence, 1982-1983; 245791 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Subseries P: Untitled/Unknown/Unpublished, 244798
      - Contract with Cosmopolitan and related materials - unnamed short story and two articles, 1948; 245936 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Contracts with Colliers and related correspondence - three unnamed short stories and one novel, 1948; 245937 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Unnamed short story and two articles - correspondence and memos with Cosmopolitan, 1948-1949; 245938 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Unnamed novel and short stories - correspondence and memos with Colliers, 1948-1949; 245940 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Untitled "On the Beach promotions piece" - letter and memo, 1959; 245941 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Claim of Walsh at Universal regarding unknown work, 1953; 245942 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Untitled play - tax and copyright issues, 1961; 245946 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Brunnenstrasse English translation with letter from Fales librarian Frank Walker, 1987; 252731 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Brunnenstrasse production at "die probebühne" - program and photocopied article, circa 1991; 252732 (Box 13, Folder 11)
        Materials are in German.
    - Subseries Q: Multiple Works, 244799
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - Remarque vs. Enterprise Productions - legal papers, 1949; 245975 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - TV file - Multiple works including Arch of Triumph and The Other Love, 1952; 245976 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Possible magazine articles, 1952; 245977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - correspondence and memos, 1951-1952; 245978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - correspondence and memos, 1953; 245979 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - Securities vs Lexington - legal papers, 1952-1953; 245980 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - Securities vs McCann - legal papers, circa 1953-1956; 245981 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Multiple works - Foreign inquiries - correspondence, 1952-1957; 245983 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Multiple works - Figaro - Operation Sunrise - legal papers, 1958; 245984 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Multiple works - Figaro - Operation Sunrise, 1958; 245982 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Figaro - Operation Sunrise - Correspondence and memoranda, 1958; 245985 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Figaro - Operation Sunrise - extra copies, 1958; 245986 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Multiple Works - Copyright correspondence and memos, 1950-1958; 246452 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Correspondence about properties for movies, 1958; 246453 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - Settlement Agreements, 1946-1960; 246454 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - drafts, 1956-1960; 246455 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Gifts of manuscripts and papers - valuations, 1959-1960; 246456 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Gifts of manuscripts and papers - duplicates and drafts of correspondence, 1960; 246457 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Contracts - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love, 1945-1961; 246458 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Contracts with Appleton Century Co Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action, 1945-1961; 246459 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Gifts of manuscripts and papers - correspondence and memos, 1959-1961; 246460 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Multiple works - extra copies and drafts, 1961-1962; 246461 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - work papers, circa 1960-1963; 246462 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - correspondence and memoranda (1 of 3), 1956-1964; 246463 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - correspondence and memoranda (2 of 3), 1956-1964; 246476 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - correspondence and memoranda (3 of 3), 1956-1964; 246477 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Copyright office search report, 1964 July 13; 246478 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Contract and related correspondence - Peebles College Edition of A Time to Love, Three Comrades and All Quiet on the Western Front, 1937-1965; 246479 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Copyright search documents and notes, 1950-1965; 246480 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Gifts of manuscripts and papers - deeds of gifts, 1959-1965; 246481 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Persian rights - All Quiet on the Western Front, The Road Back, The Night in Lisbon, 1964-1965; 246482 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Press clippings, 1966; 246483 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Mexican copyright, 1964-1969; 246484 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Book Publishing in the USSR: Reports of the Delegations of U.S. Book Publishers Visiting the USSR, 1971; 246485 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Movie - Borrowed Life, Heaven Has No Favorites, The Other Love controversy (includes contracts and agreements), 1946-1973; 246486 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Contracts and Related material - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action, 1958-1973; 246487 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Peebles College Editions, Time to Love, Three Comrades, All Quiet on the Western Front, 1958-1973; 246488 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Russian Royalties, 1972-1973; 246489 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Gifts of manuscripts, papers, books to Hebrew University of Jerusalem - correspondence and memos, 1972-1973; 246490 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Robert Lantz Agency - Correspondence and Memos, 1962-1974; 246491 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Remarque estate correspondence with Felix Guggenheim about rights to Three Comrades, All Quiet on the Western Front and others, 1973-1974; 246492 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Copyright summary of literary properties, 1973-1974; 246493 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Foreign Rights Agency - correspondence and memos, 1973-1976; 246494 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - correspondence and memoranda, 1969-1977; 246495 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Copyright assignments and certificates, 1958-1978; 246496 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Royalty statements - correspondence (1 of 3), 1950-1979; 246497 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Royalty statements - correspondence (2 of 3), 1950-1979; 246498 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Royalty statements - correspondence (3 of 3), 1950-1979; 246499 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Copyright - correspondence and memos, 1958-1980; 246500 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Putnams and Little Brown royalties statements - All Quiet on the Western Front and Three Comrades, 1936-1981; 246501 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Kiepenheuer and Witcsch, includes summary of status of publication rights of works including Arch of Triumph, Three Comrades, The Road Back, circa 1981; 246502 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Royalty statements - Harcourt, Brace and World (1 of 3), 1955-1982; 246503 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Royalty statements - Harcourt, Brace and World (2 of 3), 1955-1982; 246504 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Royalty statements - Harcourt, Brace and World (3 of 3), 1955-1982; 246505 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - correspondence and memoranda, 1978-1982; 246512 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Permissions, 1978-1982; 246513 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Arch of Triumph/The Other Love - Sunset Securities Action - memo, 1984; 246514 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Inventory of Remarque works rights internationally, circa 1985; 246515 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Royalty statements - Appleton, Century, Crofts, 1941-1986; 246516 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - German royalties correspondence, 1987; 246517 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Czechoslovakia permissions and royalties, 1984-1988; 246518 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Literary correspondence and memos, 1973-1990; 246519 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Polish royalties, 1977-1990; 246520 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Figaro - Operation Sunrise - notes, undated; 246521 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Series II: General financial and legal, 244800
    Series II: General financial and legal consists of correspondence, memos, tax returns and other financial and legal documents of Erich Remarque and Paulette Goddard not primarily related to Remarques' literary output. It is arranged chronologically.
    - 1945 Tax Audit - bills and checks, 246528 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Bank statements and slips, 1943-1945; 246529 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Astrological reading for EMR by [H. Johnson], circa 1945; 246530 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Income Tax 1945, 1944-1946; 246531 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - 1945 Tax Audit - letters and affidavits, 1946-1947; 246532 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Tax matters - correspondence and memos, 1945-1948; 246533 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Tax matters - memoranda, 1944-1949; 246534 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Tax - correspondence and memos, 1948-1949; 246535 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence and memos, 1946-1950; 246536 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Fee file, 1946-1950; 246537 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Tax - 1949, 1949-1951; 246538 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - California income tax - 1949, 1949-1951; 246539 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - General correspondence and memos, 1950-1952; 246540 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Fee file, 1951-1952; 246541 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - EMR Conference with Harriet Pilpel, 1952 June 26; 246542 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and forms regarding 1948 taxes, 1947-1954; 246543 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Lease of apartment, 1951, 1954; 246544 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 1945 income tax examination together with agents' reports and claims for refund, 1949-1954; 246545 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Tax - 1950, 1948-1955; 246546 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Tax - 1951, 1951-1955; 246547 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Tax - 1952, 1952-1955; 246548 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Tax - 1953, 1953-1956; 246549 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Personals will - note about passport, 1956; 246550 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Matrimonial - separation agreement, 1957; 246551 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Matrimonial - final settlement papers, 1957; 246552 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Security sale - correspondence and memos, 1957; 246553 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Matrimonial - divorce decree, 1957; 246554 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Matrimonial - tax, 1957; 246781 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Matriomonial - legal papers, 1956-1957; 246782 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Tax - 1954, 1954-1957; 246832 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Tax supporting papers - 1955, 1949-1958; 246833 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Erich Remarque to Harriet Pilpel, 1955-1958; 246834 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Guranty Trust Co - Deposits, 1950-1959; 246835 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Tax - 1956, 1954-1959; 246836 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Swiss tax - 1955, 1955-1959; 246837 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Erich Remarque personal will - extra copies, 1956-1959; 246838 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Taxes - 1957, 1957-1959; 246840 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Personal will - piano damage, 1958-1959; 246841 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Erich Remarque - Apartment 320 East 57th St, 1951-1960; 246842 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Tax - 1955, 1955-1960; 246843 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Erich Remarque personal will - will, 1957-1960; 246846 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Will - March 1960, 246847 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Income tax - 1958, 1958-1961; 246848 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Brochures and pamphlets about investments and legal advice, 1959-1961; 246849 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fee file - deposit Guaranty Trust - 1960, 1960-1961; 246850 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Fee file - extra copies, 1960-1961; 246851 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Plans for villa "Casa del Monte Tabor" in Porto Ronco, Switzerland, 1961; 252269 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Tax - extra copies and drafts, 1955-1962; 250803 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Matrimonial - drafts, 1957-1962; 250804 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Paulette Goddard - permanent tax, 1960-1962; 250805 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Tax - 1961, 1961-1962; 250807 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Tax - 1959 (1 of 2), 1959-1963; 250808 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Tax - 1959 (2 of 2), 1959-1963; 250809 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Tax - 1962, 1962-1963; 250810 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and memos (1 of 2), 1952-1964; 250812 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and memos (2 of 2), 1952-1964; 250813 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Tax - 1963, 1963-1964; 250814 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Tax - 1960, 1960-1964; 250816 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Erich Remarque personal will - correspondence and memos, 1955-1965; 250817 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Tax - 1964, 1964-1965; 250818 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Income tax - 1965, 1964-1965; 250819 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Tax - 1966, 1966-1967; 250820 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Tax - 1967, 1967-1969; 250821 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Tax - 1968, 1968-1969; 250823 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Remarque estate - birth certificates (copies), 1968-1969; 250825 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Remarque estate - federal estate tax work papers, 1970; 250826 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Matrimonial - correspondence and memos (1 of 2), 1956-1970; 250828 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Matrimonial - correspondence and memos (2 of 2), 1957-1970; 250830 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Remarque estate - separation agreement with Jutta Remarque, 1957-1970; 250831 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Fee file - Deposit Guaranty Trust, 1961-1970; 250837 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Tax - 1969, 1969-1970; 250838 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Remarque estate - clients' papers, 1948-1971; 250845 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Remarque estate - savings account, 1958-1971; 250846 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Remarque estate - administration (legal) papers, 1969-1971; 250847 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Remarque estate - inventory, 1970-1971; 250848 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Remarque estate - decedent's checking account, 1970-1972; 250849 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Remarque estate - correspondence, 1970-1972; 250850 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Remarque estate - social security, 1971-1972; 250852 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Remarque estate - application for tax exemption, 1972; 250853 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Remarque estate - decedent's final income tax return, 1970-1973; 250854 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Tax - 1970, 1970-1973; 250855 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Tax - 1971, 1970-1973; 250856 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Tax - 1972, 1972-1973; 250935 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Remarque Estate - Checking Account [1 of 2], 1970-1974; 251128 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Remarque Estate - Checking Account [2 of 2], 1970-1974; 251130 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Remarque Estate - Federal Estate Tax, 1971-1974; 251131 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - PG - 1973 Tax, 1972-1974; 251132 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Fees #4 [1 of 2], 1953-1975; 251134 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Fees #4 [2 of 2], 1953-1975; 251135 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Remarque Estate - Claim Jutta Remarque, 1957-1975; 251144 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - PG - Social Security, Passport, 1957-1975; 251145 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Remarque Estate - Swiss Inheritance Tax, 1963-1975; 251146 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Remarque Estate - Fiduciary Income Tax, 1970-1975; 251148 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Remarque Estate - Bills, 1970-1975; 251150 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Remarque Estate - Correspondence and Memoranda [1 of 2], 1970-1975; 251151 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Remarque Estate - Correspondence and Memoranda [2 of 2], 1970-1975; 251152 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Remarque Estate - Fees, 1970-1975; 251153 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - PG - Securities Related to Will, 1971-1975; 251154 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - PG - 1975 Tax, 251156 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Remarque Estate - Securities, 1970-1975; 251159 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Remarque Estate - Transfer of Securities, 1970-1975; 251161 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - PG - TWA Claim, 1975; 251162 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - PG - 1975 Tax - Receipts and Checks, c. 1975; 251163 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - PG - 230 57th Street Co-Op, 1973-1976; 251165 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - PG - 1974 Tax, 1974-1976; 251166 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - PG - Personal Insurance, News Item, 1976; 251167 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - PG - 1977 Income Tax, 1974-1977; 251170 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - PG - 1976 Tax, 1975-1977; 251171 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - PG - 1977 Tax, 1977-1978; 251173 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - PG - Adversary Valerian Rybar - PG Personal Papers, 1977-1978; 251175 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - PG - Adv. Valerian Rybar - Newspaper Clippings, 1978; 251176 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - PG - Adv. Valerian Rybar Inc - Extra Copies and Drafts, 1978; 251177 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - PG - Adversary Valerian Rybar - R. Weiner Construction Corp., 1978; 251178 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - PG - 1978 Tax, 251182 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - PG - Adversary Valerian Rybar Inc - Legal Papers - Supreme Court of New York, 1978; 251184 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - PG - Adversary Valerian Rybar - Legal Papers - Mechanic's Lien, 1978; 251186 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - PG - 1978 Income Tax, c. 1978; 251187 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - PG - Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Dispute with Decorator Valerian Rybar, 1978-1979; 251193 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - PG - Sale of Personal Property, 1978-1979; 251195 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - PG - Tax - Correspondence and Memos, 1957-1981; 251196 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - General - Correspondence and Memoranda [1 of 3], 1965-1981; 251198 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - General - Correspondence [2 of 3], 1965-1981; 251199 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - General - Correspondence and Memoranda [3 of 3], 1965-1981; 251201 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - PG - Andy Warhol Book, 1974-1981; 251202 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - PG - 1979-1980 Tax Data - Receipts, Bills, 1979-1981; 251204 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - PG - 1979 Taxes, 1979-1981; 251205 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - PG - 1980 Income Tax, 1979-1981; 251206 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - PG - Occidental Life Insurance, 1980-1981; 251210 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - PG - Correspondence and Memos [1 of 2], 1962-1982; 251212 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - PG - Correspondence and Memos [2 of 2], 1962-1982; 251214 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - PG - Revoked Wills, 1966-1982; 251215 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - PG - Taxes 1981, 1981-1982; 251216 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - PG - 1981 Income Tax, 1981-1982; 251217 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - PG - 1982 Taxes - Checks, Receipts, Invoices, 251609 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - PG - 1982 Income Tax, 1982-1983; 251610 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - PG - Medical Expenses 1983, 251611 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - PG - Taxes 1980 [1 of 2], 1978-1984; 251613 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - PG - Taxes 1980 [2 of 2], 1978-1984; 251617 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - PG - 1983 Taxes, 1983-1984; 251618 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - PG - H.G. Wells Memoir with Mention of Goddard, 1984; 251620 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - PG - Checking Account, 1973-1985; 251625 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - PG - 1984 Income Tax, 1983-1985; 251626 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - PG - Personal Permissions, 1985; 251627 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - PG - Will, 1971-1986; 251628 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - PG - Custody Account Morgan Guaranty, 1979-1986; 251630 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - PG - Appraisals, 1983, 1987; 251631 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - PG - Check Registers [1 of 2], 1976-1987; 251633 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - PG - Check Registers [2 of 2], 1976-1987; 251634 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - PG - Securities, 1962-1988; 251635 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - PG - General Correspondence and Memos, 1983-1988; 251637 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - PG - 1985 Taxes, 1985-1988; 251638 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - PG - 1987 Income Tax, 1987-1988; 251639 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - PG - Legal Fees, 1973-1989; 251640 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - PG - 1986 Income Tax, 1986-1989; 251643 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - PG - Purchase of Co-Op in Ritz Tower, 1976-1989; 251644 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Photocopied Articles about EMR (German), [1989]; 251645 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - PG - 1988 Income Tax, 1988-1989; 251646 (Box 33, Folder 4)